When we dropped our first single, it was the summer before my senior year.
So I came into my senior year with a hit song on the radio with my group members.
Tamika and Tasha had graduated from the school.
So it was like, you know, everybody already kind of knew us.
I'm still there, you know.
Damn, I didn't realize you were still in school.
I was still in school.
And so like when we would go do shows, when we would come home,
I still had to go to regular school.
Like I had to do work on the road, turn it in.
The day of my graduation, they were pissed at me because I went home for my graduation
when we had a show that day.
And I almost made us miss the show because the flight didn't come in on time and they were pissed.
I'm graduating.
Yeah, I was like, I don't care what y'all say.
Fuck y'all, I'm going to this graduation.
Who can I rent you?
I'm running across the stage.
I'm going to my graduation, yes.